[Music]
these are the eyes and the lies of the
taken these are the hearts but the
hearts don't be like
gos they burn cuz they are all
afraid for every one of
us there's an army of
them but you'll never fight a
alone cuz who I you
to that's the water is
ugly watch your beauty go to
me will Li you thinking of me
now these are the nights and the lights
that we fade in these are the words but
the words are coming
out they burn C St I had to
say forever
freiling
Sun there the morning
after so I'm me to you when you
go I just wanted you to
now that the wild is
[Music]
ugly watch your beautiful to
me are you thinking
ofab like a thinking of
you I would say I'm sorry
though though I really need to
go I just wanted you to
know I wanted you
to I wanted and you to
know I'm thinking have
you in Li
[Music]
every pleas are the lies and the lies of
the take can these are the hearts but
the hearts don't be like a
house never
got
afraid with my be it's twice as
hard cuz the world is
ugly but your
beautyful to
me I you
thinking I can
thinking
yeah I will say I'm sorry
though so I really
need to
go CU I just want you to
know that's the wall is
ugly what your
Bea to
me are you thinking
of you crying helpless feeling try your
eyes and start feel believe it there's
one thing they'll never take from
you in the snow in the Sun